Contact

kshchapina@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/kate-shchapina-45297957 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

ACLS

Patient Safety

Critical Care

Languages

Russian

Certifications

PALS

Basic Life Support

Advanced Cardiac Life Support

CCRN

PCCN

Kate Shchapina

Doctor of Nursing Practice - Nurse Anesthesia (DNP-NA) University of Pennsylvania, Class of 2020

Philadelphia, Pennsylvania

Summary

Upcoming CRNA, currently in the Doctoral Nurse Anesthesia program at the University of Pennsylvania, Class of 2020. SRNA portfolio includes robust clinical experience in notable institutions such as Penn Medicine, The Children's Hospital of Pennsylvania (CHOP), Fox Chase Cancer Center and Johns Hopkins Hospital.

Kate's doctoral work is in collaboration with the National Institutes of Health (NIH) and focuses on decreasing pain and opioid consumption through the implementation of Transversus Abdominus Plane (TAP) blocks in genitourinary patients undergoing abdominal surgery. Prior to graduate school, Kate worked in the Medical Intensive Care Unit (MICU) in Lenox Hill Hospital in New York City.

Experience

University of Pennsylvania School of Nursing Student Registered Nurse Anesthetist (SRNA) May 2017 - Present (3 years 3 months)

DNP Class of 2020

Lenox Hill Hospital 4 years 3 months

Registered Nurse, MICU May 2015 - April 2017 (2 years)

New York, New York

Provided care to critically ill patients with a variety of complex diagnoses including sepsis, respiratory failure, ARDS, CVAs, end-stage renal failure, encephalopathy and multi-organ system failure. Proficient in the management of vented patients, hemodynamic monitoring, vasopressor titration and CRRT initiation. Served as a preceptor and mentor to newly hired staff as well as nursing students during ongoing clinical rotations.

Registered Nurse, Step-down Telemetry

February 2013 - May 2015 (2 years 4 months)

New York, New York

Held a rotational charge role in providing care to high acuity patients requiring ongoing telemetry monitoring. Adept in the identification and interpretation of arrhythmias. Administered pulmonary toileting, blood product infusions, tube feedings, glycemic monitoring and wound care. Addressed quality of care issues including CAUTI rates and falls as the unit Safety Champion.

Education

University of Pennsylvania
DNP, Nurse Anesthesia · (2017 - 2020)

New York University
Bachelor of Science in Nursing (BSN) · (2010 - 2012)

Emory University
Registered Nurse · (2008 - 2010)

Stuyvesant High School · (2004 - 2008)